STEVE ROLLINS FULL TIME STUDENT

coding61.sr@gmail.com

**** 206-940-5274

♀ North Bend, WA

in steven-rollins

o greenhornsr

While I have spent more than 10 years as a mobility sales representative; my new passion and ambitions reside as a web developer that excels at my craft. I have spent several months primarily learning about HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REACT, REDUX, HOOKS, NODEJS, KNEX, SQL, SQLITE3, POSTGRES & more. I also have exposure to ANGULAR, MONGODB, DJANGO, PYTHON, SWIFT, & more. My goal is to find a place of employment where my passion for developing quality applications improves the quality of life & experiences for end users; increases value and I can continue to grow as a contributor with an equally strong, reciprocal team that share the same passion for life, people and developer work as I do.

Interests Include:

Molding Digital Clay(Coding)!

Lifting

Basketball

Soccer

Verizon Wireless
Mountain Region 2010
· Winner's Circle
Award given to sales
representatives performing
in the top 5% of ALL peer
Key Performance metrics
(new customers, renewed
customers, IoT, messaging,
data, etc.)

Skills

WEB DEVELOPMENT: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, React, Redux, SQL, REST, GraphQL, Python, PostgreSQL, Less/Sass, Flask, Django, Angular

Projects

Chicago Array of Things

June 2019 to June 2019

Chicago Array of Things was a project where, in 5 days, a cross functional team of UI, WEB: FE, BE, Data Scientists were expected to build out a complete web application that connected to the Chicago AOT API and rendered information that best represented environment data sourced from specific sensors a user wanted to visualize. I was FE on this project.

YELP-FEELERS Oct. 2019 to Oct. 2019

YELP FEELERS was a project where, in 5 days, a cross functional team of UI, WEB: FE, BE, Data Scientists were expected to build out a complete web application that connected to the YELP API and created the ability to MODIFY user star review scores based on substance of their written reviews to making it a more accurate depiction/review.

Education

Lambda School

Apr. 2019 to Current

Coding Dojo

Oct. 2016 to Jan. 2017

Employment

Lambda School

Team Lead(REMOTE)

North Bend, WA Aug. 2019 to Nov. 2019

Full Time position. Primary responsibility was to support the learning and professional growth of Lambda Students. Often required mentoring students in the understanding of HTML, CSS, JS, REACT, HOOKS, REDUX, CONTEXT, EXPRESS, NODE.js, SQLITE3/PSQL and other associated concepts.

Verizon Major Accounts Manager - Healthcare Bellevue, WA

June 2013 to May 2015

Responsible for identifying and introducing HIPAA compliant partner solutions that solved mobility needs of western Washington's largest healthcare systems; keeping security, industry regulations, budgets and most importantly...patient safety front of mind.

Verizon Wireless

Denver, CO

Business Account Executive

Nov. 2007 to June 2013

New business customer procurement, management of existing customer base for businesses that had employee counts mostly ranging from 5-499.

Volunteering

Mt. Si View (SVSD) · Head Coach Basketball

Developing, leading, teaching 8-11 year old boys basic and advanced basketball skills.

i-9 Sports · Flag Football Assistant Coach Teaching 6-7 year old boys Flag Football

I-9 Sports \cdot Soccer Assistant Coach

Teaching 4-5 year olds how to play soccer.